Finding Aid for the Christine Sadler Coe Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Christine Sadler Coe Papers
2016
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0084
20.06 Linear feet
Biographical Note
Ella Dillian Christine Sadler was born on April 7, 1902 in Silver Point, Tennessee. She was one of seven children of Philip Edley Sadler (1875-1951) and Frances (Fannie) Williams Sadler (1880 – 1950). She was the sister of Martha Sadler, Mary Sue Sadler and Cordell Lundy, all of Silver Point, Tennessee and of Philip Sadler of Pulaski, Virginia and James C. Sadler of Honolulu, Hawaii.
She attended Livingston Academy, Milligan College, and George Peabody College for Teachers where she received a BS degree on August 31, 1927. She earned a master’s degree in journalism from Columbia University on June 1, 1937.
She began her career in journalism as a reporter for The Nashville Banner where she worked from 1930-1936. She moved on to be a reporter for the Washington Post where she met her husband Richard Livingston Coe, who was for over 50 years a theater critic for the Washington Post. They were married in 1946. At The Washington Post she worked as a reporter, national news bureau staffer and Sunday Editor from 1937-1946.
Christine Sadler Coe was the Washington Editor of McCall’s Magazine from 1944 until her retirement in 1971. She also did special assignments for The Post and contributed to Canadian and British publications, notably The Montreal Standard. She was known professionally as Christine Sadler.
She was the first woman to cover a national political convention for The Washington Post, when in 1940 she helped cover the Republican National Convention in Philadelphia that nominated Wendell Wilkie to run against President Franklin D. Roosevelt. She continued to cover national conventions for the Washington Post and other publications for 30 years.
In addition to covering political conventions, her assignments at The Post included World War II agencies, Capitol Hill, the White House, and the funeral of President Franklin D. Roosevelt. She covered Eleanor Roosevelt’s news conferences and persuaded her to write a column for McCall’s, which Mrs. Roosevelt did from June 1949 until her death in 1962.
Christine Sadler Coe was the author of two books - America’s First Ladies (1963) and Children in the White House (1967). She personally knew all of the First Ladies from Eleanor Roosevelt to Betty Ford and many of their children, this collection reflects these personal connections in correspondence, photographs, and newspaper articles written by her and others. In 1966 she hired Lynda Bird Johnson (eldest daughter of President Lyndon Baines Johnson), now Mrs. Charles Robb, to work for McCall’s.
At the time of her death she was working on a collection of 50 letters by Nellie Parke Custis, stepdaughter of George Washington, which was to be called America’s First Princess. Mrs. Coe’s research for this collection of letters makes up a substantial part of the WRITINGS series in these papers.
Among her notable achievements and honors that she received was being chosen to view the Berlin Airlift (Operation Vittles) which took place from 1948-1949. She served as the president of the Women’s National Press Club (now the Washington Press Club) from 1942-43 and as chairman of its 50th Anniversary Committee in 1970. She was also a member of the American Newspaper Women’s Club; an honorary member of Theta Sigma Phi; and a member of National Women’s Democratic Club.
From 1956 through 1959 she was appointed and served as a charter member of the Defense Department Advisory Committee on Women in the Services (DACOWITS). Mrs. Coe frequently was a guest on radio and television programs. She was one of ten women selected by State Department to be the guest of the German government while exploring uses to the Marshall Plan funds. This official tour in July 1964 was made in memory of President John F. Kennedy.
She was elected to the George Peabody College Board of Trust in May 1968, and she was on the board at the time of the historic merger of Peabody with Vanderbilt University in 1979.
Christine Sadler married Richard Livingston Coe (1914-1995) in 1946. He was the theater critic for The Washington Post for fifty years. He became Critic Emeritus in 1979. He was instrumental in establishing the John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts in the nation’s capital and in efforts to end racial discrimination of African Americans attending The National Theatre prior to the civil rights movement. Mr. Coe received the Critic of the Year award by the Director’s Guild of America in 1963, and is an inductee in the College of Fellows of the American Theatre.
Richard Coe’s early newspaper articles for the Stars and Stripes, a U.S. Army newspaper publication and his letters to his wife are well represented in these papers, in addition to the collection of later newspaper articles that he wrote for The Washington Post.
The Coes lived in Georgetown at 2713 Dumbarton Avenue, Washington D.C. Mrs. Coe gardened there in “their little shaded spot” and was a “Saturday painter” studying under Nancy (Mrs. Estes) Kefauver, and exchanged paintings with other amateur artists including Beatrice Lillie, Tony Curtis, Carol Channing, and Shirley Booth. Some of her artwork is included in these papers.
Christine Sadler Coe died of cardiac arrest on June 25, 1983 at George Washington University Hospital in Washington, D.C. at the age of 81. Richard Livingston Coe died November 12, 1995.
Scope and Content Note
The Coe papers consist of 20.06 linear feet and contain a wealth of material relating to Christine Sadler Coe’s life long career in journalism and to that of her husband, Richard Coe who was the longtime theater critic for the Washington Post. The papers are comprised of seven series which document her life as well as the mid-century events and crises of America and the world. A leader in the field of journalism her papers follow her career trajectory and experiences as a female journalist in a male dominated field.
In the Writings Series are manuscripts and research for her two books America’s First Ladies (1963) and Children in the White House (1967) and for an unfinished work on Nelly Parke Custis, descendant of George Washington. Also significant in this collection are articles she wrote for the Washington Post and McCall’s magazine; and correspondence, invitations, programs, notebooks, and photographs that reflect her many personal and professional friendships with first families, ambassadors, politicians, and other prominent figures in Washington, D.C. in the four decades that she lived there.
- Correspondence-Incoming
  - Ahlgren – Atomic (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bader – Butwin (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cahn – Chennault (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Christian Science Monitor – Clark (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Coe, Richard L., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Coe, Richard L., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Coe, Richard L., March 11, 1943 – November 10, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Coe, Richard L., December 1943 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Coe, Richard L., January – June 1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Coe, Richard L., July – November 1944 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Coe, Richard L., February 13 – May 25, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Coe, Richard L., June 3 – July 23, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Coe, Richard L., July 27 – September 7, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Coe, Richard L., September 21 – October 29, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Coe, Richard L., November 2 – December 23, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Coe, Richard L., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Coe, Richard L. – undated from the 1940’s (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Correspondence – Incoming
  - Coe, Richard L., 1951 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Coe, Richard L., 1952 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Coe, Richard L., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Coe, Richard L., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Coe, Richard L., 1959 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Coe, Richard L., 1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Coe, Richard L., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Coe, Richard L., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Coe, Richard L., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Coe, Richard L., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Coe, Richard L., 1966-67 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Coe, Richard L., 1970-79 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Coe, Richard L., undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Coe, Richard L., undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Coe, Robert – Culligan (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Correspondence –Incoming
  - Davidson – Duke (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Easter – Evins (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Federal Emergency Administration – Funk (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Gable – Guyol (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Halifax – Hershey (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Hill – Ingram (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Johnson – Knox (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - L. – Lourie (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Lundy (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Lundy, Ted (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Lundy, Tina (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - MacCampbell, Donald (agent), 1962 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - MacCampbell, Donald (agent), 1963-65 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - MacCampbell, Donald (agent) – 1967 – 1970 – MacFadden (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Mademoiselle, 1939–43 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Mamedova – Matthews (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Correspondence – Incoming
  - Mayes, Herbert R. (president of McCalls), 1963-65 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Mayes, Herbert R. (president of McCalls), 1966-1977; undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - McCalls (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - McCalls (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - McCalls (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - McDonald – McWilliams (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Meadors – Murphy (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - National Defense Conference, January 1952 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Nehru – Oliver (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Park – Priest (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Publishers – Putnam, G.P. (William Targ, editor) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Randolph – Richards (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Robb, Lynda Bird Johnson - Ross (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Sadler family (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Sadler, Edley (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Sadler, Ellen – Sadler, Schley (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Sadler, Fritz and Mary Sue (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Sadler, James and Nancy, family (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Sadler, Philip, family (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Sadler, R.C. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Schendel – Smith (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Soviet – Strom (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Correspondence – Incoming
  - Tate – Tully (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Waldrop – Worden (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified - family (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - The White House (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Invitations
  - The White House – President and Mrs. Franklin D. Roosevelt (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The White House – President and Mrs. Franklin D. Roosevelt (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The White House – President and Mrs. Harry Truman (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The White House – President and Mrs. Dwight D. Eisenhower (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The White House – President and Mrs. John F. Kennedy (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The White House – President and Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The White House – President and Mrs. Richard M. Nixon (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - The White House – President and Mrs. Gerald Ford (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - The White House – President and Mrs. Jimmy Carter (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - The White House – President elect Ronald Reagan (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - U.S. Officials (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Ambassadors/Embassies – A-E (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Ambassadors/Embassies – F-H (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Ambassadors/Embassies – I (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Ambassadors/Embassies – J-L (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Ambassadors/Embassies – M-Q (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Ambassadors/Embassies – R-S (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Invitations
  - Ambassadors/Embassies – T-Z (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Ambassadors/Embassies – unidentified (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Press Clubs (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Personal A-C (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Personal D-F (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Personal G (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Personal H-L (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Personal M (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Personal N-O (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Personal P – S (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Personal T-Z (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Unidentified – alphabetized by first name (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Unidentified – 1930’s (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Unidentified – 1940’s (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Unidentified – 1950’s (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified – 1960’s (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Unidentified – 1970’s (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Unidentified – 1980’s; 1990’s (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Unidentified – Christmas cards (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Unidentified (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Personal and Biographical
  - Birth certificate, April 7, 1902 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Memorabilia, 1920’s (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Grammar Grade’s Teacher’s Certificate, July 1, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Transcript Milligan College, December 8, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Diploma, George Peabody College for Teachers, August 31, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Program, George Peabody College for Teachers, August 31, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - High School Teaching Certificate, August 31, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - WPA ( Works Progress Administration) – Press Release, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Diploma – Columbia School of Journalism, June 1, 1937 ( in Flat Box #45) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Columbia School of Journalism, Commencement, Alumni Activities, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Columbia School of Journalism, “the First Fifteen Years” Class of 1937 Alumni Publication and other (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Engagement announcement in the Nashville Banner –, March 20, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Apartment rental, 1946-1950 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - National Citizens’ Committee, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - California Saga of Rose McKee and Christine Sadler, August 1956 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Commemorative Stamp presented to CSC by JFK, October 11, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Robb, Lynda B. Johnson – Newspaper clippings, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - National Association of Real Estate Boards Invitation to Speak, November 1967 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Brief biography, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Art by CSC and others –exhibits (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Christmas Cards designed by CSC (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Personal calendar for, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Coe’s Georgetown House and Tour Newspaper articles and related materials, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Membership cards – press passes – U.S. Congress (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Membership cards – Press Clubs (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Membership cards/passes – Special Events, 1935 -1956 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Membership cards – Authors Guild and other (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Memorabilia – tickets, menus, etc… (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Personalized McCall’s note paper; name cards (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Memorabilia, Correspondence – Coe, Richard L. (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson family note to Richard L. Coe, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Coe, Richard L. – articles (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Coe, Robert L. - articles (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Personal and Biographical
  - Articles about Christine Sadler Coe 1930’s – 1940’s (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Articles about Christine Sadler Coe 1950’s (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Articles about Christine Sadler Coe1950’s (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Articles about Christine Sadler Coe 1960’s (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Articles about Christine Sadler Coe 1960’s (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Articles about Christine Sadler Coe 1960’s (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Articles about Christine Sadler Coe 1970’s (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Articles about Christine Sadler Coe 1970’s (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Articles about Christine Sadler Coe Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Articles about Christine Sadler Coe Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Family – Sadler, Philip M. – Political career (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Family – Sadler, Philip M. – Military service (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Family – Sadler, Philip Edley – Genealogy and Children (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Family – Sadlers (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Family – Tennessee/Putnam County (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Family – Newspaper clippings (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Personal and Biographical - Activities and Organizations
  - Programs (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Federation of Women’s Clubs of Arlington County, Virginia Yearbook, 1964-65 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Garden Clubs (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Personal and Biographical - Activities and Organizations – George Peabody College for Teachers
  - Correspondence, 1968-1974 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence – Gift Acknowledgement, 1969-1977 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence – 1979 – Merger with Vanderbilt (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Invitations (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Member Lists – 1968 – (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Member Lists (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Peabody Alumni, D.C. – list (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Susan Riley endowment (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Articles, 1968-1977 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, June 1974 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Personal and Biographical
  - Story of expedition to find Walt Rostow’s house in Texas (LBJ) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Travel – Study Tour of Eastern Europe, June 1 – 22, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Travel – keepsakes (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Travel – Williamsburg, Virginia – postcards (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Nashville Banner – clippings (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings about others (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings about others (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Collection of publications/pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Collection of publications/pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Miscellany (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Miscellany (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Career in Journalism
  - Columbia University Graduate School of Journalism – “Growing Pens” 5th Anniversary Issue, June 1942 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Presidency of the Women’s National Press Club, 1942 -43, correspondence and letters of congratulations (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Presidency of the Women’s National Press Club, 1942-43, correspondence (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Presidency of the Women’s National Press Club, 1942-43, correspondence (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Presidency of the Women’s National Press Club, 1942-43, correspondence and announcements (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Presidency of the Women’s National Press Club, 1942-43, newspaper articles about CSC (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Presidency of the Women’s National Press Club, 1942 -43, newspaper articles (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Presidency of the Women’s National Press Club, 1942-43, newspaper articles (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Presidency of the Women’s National Press Club, 1942-43, newspaper articles (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Career in Journalism - Correspondence and Memberships
  - Montreal Standard – Correspondence, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Mrs. Roosevelt’s Press Conference Association and other, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Washington Press Club – Directories (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Washington Press Club – Directories (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Women’s National Press Club – Cookbook, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Women’s National Press Club – Directories, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Women’s National Press Club – 50th Anniversary Dinner, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Women’s National Press Club – Invitations (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Women’s National Press Club – programs (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Women’s National Press Club – press releases (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Women’s National Press Club – news articles on CSC as WNPC president (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Women’s National Democratic Club –“Jenny for President”, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Women’s National Democratic Club (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - American Newspaper Women’s Club – Membership Directories, 1972-1975 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Congressional Clubs – programs (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - United Church Women – correspondence (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Woman’s Club of Fowler, Indiana (America’s First Ladies) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Club Memberships – Pisces; Theta Sigma Phi (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Clubs – programs (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Career in Journalism
  - McCall’s – Employment – Insurance and Retirement (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - McCall’s –Business, 1952-53 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - McCall’s Club Notes, October 1955 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - McCall’s – Business (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - McCall’s in the News, October 1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Western trip – notebook, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Visit to Mexico, March 1952 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - The Banner – death of Mrs. James G. Stahlman, March 1952 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Notebook, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Trip to West Coast, San Francisco, and Malibu, August 1967 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Notebooks, 1969-1979 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Notebook, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - London trip May 20 – June 20, 1977 – notebook (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Research notebooks (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Research notebooks (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Research notebooks (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Research notebooks (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Research notebooks – pages (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Presidential coverage – Hoover, Herbert – Inauguration, March 4, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Presidential coverage – Roosevelt, Franklin D. – Inauguration, January 20, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Presidential coverage – Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Career in Journalism – Presidential Coverage
  - Truman, Harry S. – Inauguration, January 19, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D. – Inauguration, January 19, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight, D. – Inauguration, January 21, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Kennedy, John F. – as Senator (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Kennedy, John F. – Inauguration, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Kennedy, John F. – Inaugural Parade, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Kennedy, John F. – Inauguration – 1961 – Official Program, Invitations, other (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Kennedy, John F. – Inauguration, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Kennedy, John F. – News articles (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Kennedy, John F. – News articles (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Kennedy, John F. – The Arts/remarks (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Kennedy, John F. - The Arts/ draft of article (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Kennedy, John F. - The Arts (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Kennedy, John F. - The Arts (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Kennedy, John F. – Assassination (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – Invitations and Programs, 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – 1963 – News articles (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – 1963 – News articles (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Career in Journalism – Presidential Coverage
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1964 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – 1964 – Text of Address at the Kennedy Center, December 3rd (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – Inauguration Address, January 1965 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – Inauguration – January 1965- programs and memorabilia (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – Inauguration – January 1965 – news articles (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – Address to Congress “The White House Message on Natural Beauty” (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – 1965 – 1968 – news articles on Lady Bird Johnson (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – events at the White House/Mrs. Johnson (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – April 9, 1965 – National Council on the Arts (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. –Arts Events, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – 1965 – news articles (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – 1965 – news articles (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – 1966 – news articles (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – undated news articles c. 1966? (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – 1967 – news articles (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – 1967 – news articles (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – 1967 – news articles (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – 1967 – news articles (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Career in Journalism – Presidential Coverage
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – 1968 – news articles (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. – 1968 – news articles – the arts, other (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. -1968 – news articles (Box 14, Folder 3)